{
    "id": "9a2e8c6e6a0247d2bac4fa797febad1d",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He began to play guitar when he ............................... six.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "94090a02e4a34579837db6a179a58c02"
        },
        {
            "question": "He started talking about his pet projects, but everybody ................................... out of the room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "goes",
                "went",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a2dbc9b8c7924c6c91b1725a998161e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I looked out of the window and saw Susie ..................................... down the street.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to drive",
                "driving",
                "drove"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ac5a261f6649440a979f550a2e1dcd04"
        },
        {
            "question": "My legs were stiff because I ......................................... standing still for a long time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "have been",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fc24e2b106194b3eb3a9e6c1dce029cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wondered who ................................... the money.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "took",
                "has taken",
                "had taken"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "462c696c54c246a5bf3e9bea7fb303fd"
        },
        {
            "question": "After he finished his exams, he .................................. to New York for a month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "goes",
                "went",
                "has gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f60eff1e78c94fa89953870bcd1770b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "We eat that we ..................................... live.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "must",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c6efe80f1e814477b0626bd4715e4229"
        },
        {
            "question": "I donâ€™t know ............................... she will come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "whether",
                "weather"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b17449faed18400796c21784f07204bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "If they ..................................... him to a good hospital, he would have survived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have taken",
                "took",
                "had taken"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d87d572acf49442e92327fcce06048df"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the girl ...................................... won the first prize.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "which",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "aa48f4c5e4ec4c2ca25ab390a26ecf6f"
        }
    ]
}